negative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
mmm
Thank you for watching to the end.
See you in the next video.
[Fast forward]
[Fast forward] [Fast forward]
Yuzuki's room has started!
Yay!
Yes, it's me, Team Killer Whale, Purple Purple Kakari!
I'm Yuzuki Ogle. Please give me your best regards!
Today is my solo Yuzuki's Room because Mr. Setoguchi is absent. Yuzuki's Room is a live broadcast on our youtube orca channel every Monday from 9:00 p.m.
Yuzuki's Room" is a live broadcast on youtube channel from 9pm every Monday, where Yuzuki and Setoguchi from Scrap, a well-known game of real de-gaming, sometimes welcome guests and talk about various topics.
We will be doing a live broadcast with guests from Scrap and Yuzuki Oguura, the orca who is well-known for his real-life de-gaming.
If you are watching this live broadcast, you are my roommate, and I will call you my roommate during this time.
Oh no!
Talking by myself!
So, how many years has it been since you were in Yuzuki's room without Mr. Setoguchi?
It's been about two years? It's been since we were still in the double digits, right?
It's been so long.
It's been a while since Yuzuki cried in your letter.
That's right. It was in the last room.
It's been a long time. I'm used to it now that Setoguchi-san's absent.
I'm going to do my best on my own.
Let's go to the first corner!
This week's shirk
This corner is to review the week of my team, Shazi.
Let's see, this week...
I did a lot of work that I can't tell you about...
I did a lot of work that I can't tell you about, and I'm a little bit excited about the release of ep on June 28th.
I've been doing a lot of shooting for it and other things, and, of course, there's the free event release on the weekend.
And, of course, there was a free event "release" on the weekend!
June 10, we went to Iwata, Shizuoka. It was the first time for us to perform in Iwata, and the first time for us to perform in Shizuoka.
It's been about 23 434 years since I was on a tour called "Isekukan Tour"... I don't know.
I don't know, it's been 34 years, 3 years, 3 years since I've been in Shizuoka, but thank you all for coming to see us!
I was wondering if the weather would be OK, because the weather was very dangerous and the location of Laraport Iwata was very dangerous.
So I wondered if it would be okay, but the weather held up for two minutes, and it was hot and humid, and I worked up a good sweat and we were able to do the show.
The scoring session was also outside, so...
I'm not good at answering questions.
I'm used to it. I'll miss you.
Hello, I'm Mizukami from Scrap Sales.
I see... you're a bot today.
Thank you very much for working on it.
And Sunday, yesterday, we had a free live concert at Ohtaka, Aichi Prefecture.
Oh!
We had a special event where we tried for the first time to have the audience be captivated by the music and just stare at each other for a few hours.
We had a special event for the first time, where we just stared at each other for a couple of hours.
It's not like we're going to record our true feelings or anything, but it's just a time for the two of us to be together, which is the most powerful thing ever.
It's not that I'm going to leave a record of my true feelings or anything like that, but it's just that the two of us spent the whole time together, which is the most powerful thing ever.
We'll have a big bear in honor of the departing bears, and we'll change the special event a little bit.
8 where was it again?
Kameido Kameido is in the Kanto area, but I hope you'll look forward to it.
I'm sure you'll enjoy it.
Thank you very much.
That's right.
And just now we had our monthly live broadcast of the one-person loincloth girl show.
I'm a bit shy and live in Aichi Prefecture, so I'll be doing live broadcasts in Tokyo.
So, I thought it would be a good opportunity for me to make friends with idols through this program.
So today, Hitomi Ara from TOKYO GIRLS' STYLE was our first guest for the first episode of the program and she came to talk to us about her experiences in the past.
I was really nervous at first, but we found a lot of things we have in common, and we were able to exchange lines without incident.
That's amazing!
If we exchange lines, we're friends, right?
That's right.
I think so, don't you?
I think so.
Yes, thank you.
And, you know, with Hii-chan, we took pictures afterwards and sent them to each other.
And, you know, we took pictures and sent them to each other, and asked to go to a cafe.
Let's go to a café, or invite her when she's in Tokyo.
We exchanged a few messages.
We exchanged a few messages...you know...
I'm not sure how the theme of this program will lead to the future.
I'm looking forward to seeing how the theme of this show will lead to the future.
Please look forward to it!
I'm also looking forward to next month's guest.
I was really, really nervous.
I was really nervous.
But recently, thanks to Yuzuki's funny face
But, my "hinomimi" is getting better little by little, thanks to Yuzuki's funny face.
It's really just a little bit, about the size of a pea.
So, if I have a one-person loincloth, I can borrow the power of Yuzuki's funny face.
With the help of Yuzuki's funny face
I'd like to become a little more attractive as soon as possible.I'm hoping to get a little sooner rather than later, and I'd like to get a little more charming and high-minded.
Please look forward to Yuzuki's growth in that area as well!
Well, Killer Whale, that's all for this week!
It's so fast. It's going so fast, isn't it? But today, I'd like to continue with Yuzuki's hair festival finish.
I hope you can read as many messages as possible, so please watch until the end!
And now, this week's STOPLAR news!
This is a corner where we introduce you to Taichan, Iginari and Okusan, who are local members of StarLastPlanet, to which we belong.
BASHO-chan will soon celebrate her 8th anniversary, and she's had a lot of great events, including a live concert in Paris.
I'm most interested in the "Music Day" concert in Fukuoka on August 11 and in Tokyo on August 20.
August 20 in Tokyo!
The setlist will be based on the requests from the members of the group.
I'm personally interested in BASHO-chan's band formation, and I'm also interested in the set list based on the requests from the audience.
I'm also concerned about Basho's band composition, and I think it's something you have to have a strong relationship of trust with him to make a setlist based on a request.
I think the bond between the band members and Bashochan will be strengthened and we will be able to see a new side of Bashochan at this concert. I hope you will all enjoy the show and join us!
Next up are Iginali and his wife, Ms. Touhoku, who reads what our leader, Hanako Tachibana, gives us every week, so I'd like to read them again this week.
Yuzuki-chan, it's good to see you again today.
I miss you, Yuzuki-chan, and so do I. This week, Mrs. Yuzuki and Mr. Yuzuki had a collaboration event with Vegalta Vegalta Sendai of the Japan J-League.
We had a live performance at the stadium and collaborated with the chair-leader, which was a lot of fun.
I was able to watch the game, and I was very encouraged by the way they were trying to win the game with all their might.
Since I have been appointed as a cheerleading ambassador, I would like to accumulate virtues in my daily life so that I can become a goddess of victory.
I wish you all a wonderful day tomorrow as well!
And thank you very much.
I saw some off-shot photos of the stadium on each of your instagrams.
We are also cheering for the Grand Bassin in Nagoya, so I can understand how it gives you courage.
When we win the games we go to, we think we might be the goddess of victory.
But it's because I feel that way that I want to go to more games, and I hope you all enjoy watching sports, too.
I'm sure you all would like to go to sports games and watch sports too.
So if you are looking for a way to get some exercise or relieve some of your daily stress, I really recommend watching sports.
This week's Upper Wrapper
Next is this week's Nairuna!
This corner is a recap of a week in the life of one of our semi-regular upper rappers, Lulu Luna.
Yesterday at the free live, there was a person who said she was watching Yuzuki's version along with Lulu's Luna and Konruna,
I told him to watch it from the beginning to the end, so he said, "Are you watching? Are you watching?
I told her to watch it from the beginning to the end, so I said, "Are you watching? Please watch it all the way through.
Then, I will read it, believing that you are watching it.
Good evening, Yuzuki-chan and roommates. This is Naitruna this week.
This week I had the pleasure of appearing at Tokyo Yakan Land. Thank you to everyone who came.
This is the second time YakanLand itself has been held, and it was my first time to perform.
Almost all of the performers were first-timers, so I was a little rusty, but I think that helped to deepen our relationship.
There is something like snow, but here is a question for Sleeman. Is Sleeman here?
Is there a Sleeman?
I think Sleeman is here, so I just want him to ask me the question, but should I wait for Sleeman to come?
Yes, I think so.
Do you think so?
I think he's already here.
Be careful on the way. Sleiman?
Watch out!
Hey!
Sleeman, he can talk!
Sleeman!
Oh, I'm talking!
I'll go now. Sleeman, we have a question from Mr. Rumpin.
Here's the problem.
Don't hurt yourself, I promise.
Are you okay? Sleeman.
How are you? Are you okay?
Okay, we'll just keep working on the problem.
Really?
How many roles did I play?
I didn't hear the first part.
What role did you play in Tokyo Yakan Land, Mr. Lumpin?
Yakan?
That is correct!
I played the younger sister of Rinati's twin daughters.
Congratulations!
Yes, Slima, you are correct, I played the younger sister of Rinati's daughter.
Thank you, Surima.
Are you okay?
I'm fine now.
Thank you. Thank you.
I'm worried about you... you're half a tree man... ok, ok.
I never thought I'd play the role of a baby in my life, but here I am, playing the role of a baby.
Of course, there was also a special cover song for the day, as Ruri and I covered Femme Fatale's "Daiko Daiko Kyu Daishugi" and we also performed "Dance Hall," "Blue Lightning," and "Everybody's a Baby.
We sang Dance Hall, Blue Lightning, and all of us sang and danced together with hb 48, 48's River, and many other combinations.
And Yuzuki-chan is going to perform at the next Yoruhen Land, right? I was so excited when she announced it on stage, and I'm so happy to be able to work with her again!
We had a lot of other fun things happen this week, but I'll tell you about them later. Thank you again for your support this week, and I'll see you again at Lunatics Time or some other time!
That's all for this week's Nairuna!
Thank you very much.
There's an event called Tokyo Night Land where there are performances, songs, covers, talks, etc.
I'm going to perform for the third time at the Tokyo Kinema Club in September.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to it.Thank you very much.
Let's talk about my personal life.
I'll tell you about my personal life.
Last time Amefura was here as a guest.
I've been on LINE with Hana-chan every day.
We've been strengthening our bond.
I'm also on line with Yuzu-chan.
We've been talking about going out to eat together, the four of us.
Yuzuki has a favorite restaurant.
There's a restaurant that she loves so much.
I thought I'd like to take her there.
I suggested it to Hana-chan.
I suggested it to Hana-chan, and she really liked pizza.
I was the one who recommended it.
And she was so happy.
I'd like to tell you guys about it on instagram.
I'd like to report about it on my instagram.
So please look forward to it!
I've also been in touch with Ayame Kase of Ukka every day.
I've already made plans to hang out with Ayame.
We've already decided where we're going to go.
So please wait for my insta-report!
Anything else you want to ask?
In the current free live show, there is a time when you are allowed to take pictures and a time when it's OK to take pictures.
There is a time when it's OK to take pictures.
After the show, there is a time for everyone to take pictures.
I'd like to know how many photos you took and how many people saved them.
We talked about it at the show.
I was talking about it at the concert.
I recently made my preservation debut.
It's amazing! I've saved so many!
Well, not so much "a lot" as "a lot"...
I saved 5 photos in 2 days!
Everyone is taking great pictures.
I'm going to save more and more of them.
I don't know, it's different from the live photos, but it's more dynamic... You don't usually get photos for instagram, photos that are not just set photos...
So I think that kind of thing is a little refreshing, and I save a lot of photos like this.
If there are any cute pictures of Amefura-chan, please tag me.
If you have any cute pictures of Amehura-chan, please tag her. If you find any cute pictures of Amehura-chan, please tag her. Right........ Yes, thank you.
By the way, Ms. Mizukami, is there a girl in StarPlaza that you like? Oh, yes.
It's difficult. I don't know, you were saying Moa-chan's, Moa-chan's before, right? Slither Moa-chan, Uka-no-nee. You know, Moa-chan's name was mentioned a little.
I used to mention Moa-chan's name, and Moa-chan's name was mentioned a little bit, but now, Moa-chan came the other day, and there are many people who come to Yuzuki's room, and you can watch Yuzuki's hair festival, but do you like her?
Do you know if you like this girl?
Let's see...
Yes, I do. Yes, yes, she is a BOT.
Do you like them all?
Everyone likes her.
It's not the most spread out.
Okay, what about the fake dad?
Turn around and turn into an arrow...
I like you, Seta.
Oh, Seta Sakura.
Cute.
She's cute.
You like her when you see her live?
When I saw them live, and also when I got to say hello to them.
And the live broadcast. The whole thing was live.
When you came to our New Year's special.
When she came to the show.
I thought she was a big eater.
The first New Year's special?
That's right.
When he wasn't a fake dad.
Oh, he's always been a fake.
I've always been a dad.
When you're a dad, but not a fake dad.
Right.
You're right, Chanchan, you're very destructive.
Thank you.
Hey, just like that.
There are a lot of really great kids in the staff run.
Recently, there are more and more sites that allow photography.
I've seen it on TikTok and other places, and it's really cool.
I've been watching TikTok, and I've seen a lot of Tohoku-san and others.
I'd love it if you could send that kind of information to TikTok and so on.
If you could post them on TikTok or something, it might get a lot of attention.
If you send them to TikTok, they might get a lot of buzz.
Please upload a lot of photos to TikTok!
I'd appreciate it.
Okay, I'll do one more thing here.
Yuzuki's hair festival.
Yuzuki Daikoku made a vlog of a day in the life of Yuzuki Daikoku, or the making of Yuzuki Daikoku.
It will be up on youtube soon.
But before that, we've just finished the trailer, and we'd like you all to have a look at it here.
Are you ready for it?
Let's see!
How did you like it?
I love it!
I want to see more Life of the Shirt!
Wait a minute.
Is that possible?
It's fun!
Thank you very much for your time.
I think there's a lot of stuff in this short trailer that I'm interested in.
How long is it? 30 to 40 minutes.
We will soon be releasing a very long movie that will be 30 to 40 minutes long, so please look forward to it.
I'm currently editing it to rave reviews.
I'm editing a lot of stuff on youtube lately.
I've been uploading a lot of things on youtube.
Until the video is released, I hope you will enjoy the videos of other presidents.
Please look forward to it.Looking forward to it!
Thank you very much.
Let's introduce Yuzuki's Hair Festival Impressions in this corner!
We held Yuzuki's Hair Festival at ZEPP Shinjuku on June 3.
We've been receiving a lot of feedbacks about the event, and we'd like to thank you all for that.
I introduced some of them last week.
I introduced some of them last week, but due to time constraints, I only had time to introduce a few.
So today, I'd like to show you a lot of them.
More applause!
Thank you very much for all the applause!
We received a lot of applications... not applications...
It's not an application.
Thank you very much for all of them.
I'll go in order.
I'll start with room name Oka-chan.
Yuzuki, Setoguchi-san.
This was last week, so good evening to everyone from AmeFlash!
Thank you so much for a great time at Yuzuki's Hair Fest!
Especially you, Yuzuki and Setoguchi, and all the Stapler students.
Yuzuki's Hair Fest family
Thank you so much for your hard work on the first two parts of the event!
Thank you so much for your hard work!
I could talk about my impressions of this event until morning.
I'll try to keep it short.
First of all, I would like to talk about one part of Lumaiglo.
Setoguchi's choice was too good!
Thank you so much!
I was hoping to hear Yuzuki's song "Hatsukoi Cider" at the birthday party.
And to my surprise, it was Hatsukoi Cider that started it all!
To be honest, I almost fell to my knees!
At this point, I knew I had come to the right place!
And even when the second song was "Hot Up"...
I was super happy with those two songs alone, so thank you so much!
And secondly, it was so much fun to see Yuzuki-chan, the nerd!
Needless to say, everyone's performance was wonderful, but I really enjoyed seeing Yuzuki-chan, Nukehira-chan, Amehra-chan, and
Nukegai-chan, Amefura-chan, Tohoku-san, and Team Shachi.
I was very happy to see Yuzuki Daikoku as an otaku!
I hope that Yuzuki's Hair Fest will continue to be an annual event for many, many years to come.
I hope that Yuzuki's Hair Fest will continue to be an annual event for many, many years to come!
Not to mention next year and beyond.
Desu, right?
Death, yes.
It's a festival, isn't it?
It's a festival.
I'm sorry, I fell for it.
I'd be happy to see you again before the end of the year, if not next year!
Thank you so much for a great time!
PS, the interplay between Azu, Yuzuki the expert, and Karen the expert was a rock!
Thank you very much.
Applause
Thank you very much
I'm so glad
We've had quite a response to Hatsukoi Cider as well.
The same goes for Hot Up.
The set list is quite unexpected.
Those songs were decided by the three of us in Rumiguru.
What did you think when you received it?
When it arrived?
But we decided to play Hatsukoi Cider, right?
When we decided to do it, we wanted it to be the first song.
And I wanted the first song to be a cappella.
So we had them do it.
It was great to see Daikoku-san hit the light in the middle of the empty space and start singing.
It must have been a great feeling to start singing in the middle of the empty space, wasn't it?
I was shaking! I was shaking!
My hands were sweating so much before the show started.
My voice was almost shaking.
But it felt so good!
I got the impression that she sang with a lot of energy.
It's my favorite song, so I'm going to sing it in voice training.
I was asked "Is this your favorite song? I was asked.
My voice teacher asked me
She said, "It's my favorite song.
I told him that it's a Halo Pro song that I want.
I knew it. Your voice is totally different.
I enjoy singing all the songs.
But when the nerd feeling comes in, it's like a little bit of deron.
But when the nerd feeling comes in, the sweetness comes in as a nuance.
I had so much fun that you said so.
I had so much fun that I was able to do Rumai Glow.
Yuzuki-chan from Amefura joined last time?
I think there was a feeling of
I hope you'll look forward to it as well.
To the sequel.
I don't think there's much going on in the story.
Once Yuzuki's hair festival is decided...
I'm sure we'll talk about it and see where we go from there.
I'd love for you to be in it.
So please do.
Looking forward to it!
Thank you, Okachan!
In the making-of video we're making right now.
I've included the a cappella part in the making-of video I'm making now.
So for those of you who couldn't make it.
I wanted to make it a premiere.
If you could watch it then...
If it's a problem with YouTube's terms and conditions
I'll probably take it down.
That's right.
It's a cappella, so I'm hoping it'll be good.I'm a cappella, so I'm hoping I'll be able to do a little bit of it.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you very much.
Please look forward to it!
Next, we have room name Yasuuke!
I attended both parts of Yuzuki's Hair Fest 2023!
The performances of all the groups were great, but
I wrote my impressions specifically for the group that was there this time!
You must be Amefura-chan!
First of all, Amehura-chan!
I was very impressed with their stylish music that fit the venue of ZEPP Shinjuku
I was very impressed with how well they fit in the box at ZEPP Shinjuku.
I was especially impressed by their performance using a stand, which is not something you usually see
It was so cool!
Your stirring performance of "Metamorphose" was great!
I'm going to listen to them more and more from now on!
And Team Shachi!
It was the first time for me to participate in an orca performance where I could speak out loud.
I strongly felt that the heart and soul of the orcas is in the call!
The most powerful one was "Ultra Miracle Super Belly Belly".
Ultra super miracle super belly power ball!
I had originally heard the live soundtrack of 2018 on Subscribe.
It left a great impression on me, and I was looking forward to when I would be able to experience it.
I was looking forward to when I could experience it myself!
And then the second part of the hair festival
The combination of calls and headbangs
I was overwhelmed by the energy of this song that was fully formed by the combination of calls and headbangs.
The members' head banging was so cool that it made me jump out of my skin!
And the ending of the song, which has become a Hair Fest specialty!
The performers were all so neat and tidy, enjoying life to the fullest!
Mr. Setoguchi waving his towel around on the stand and getting into the groove!
Nise Papa watching the entire stage with warm eyes
Ogawa-san's dance moves are really sharp!
Mizukami-san making a heart for Tohoku-san's Date-san!
Wait, what does this mean?
I'll get to the bottom of it later.
I'll read it one more time.
Mr. Mizukami making hearts with Mr. Date of Tohoku.
And Mr. Treeman, who somehow came out only for the second part of the show.
There was so much information on stage that it made me dizzy!
The warm and relaxed atmosphere of Yugatsu's room was recreated.
Mr. Daikoku, Mr. Setoguchi and everyone involved
Thank you very much for organizing another wonderful event this year!
I will continue to support Yuguki's Room!
PS, the person in front of me had Mr. Mizukami's mask on the back of his head.
Mr. Mizukami's mask on the back of his head.
In other words, I and Mr. Mizukami's masks were facing each other.
In the darkness, I could see the white eyes? White eyes? White eyes.
It was a little scary to see Mr. Mizukami with white eyes in my line of sight.
Thank you very much.
There was one thing I wanted to mention.
Mr. Mizukami making hearts with Mr. Date from Tohoku...
From my point of view as a member of the audience...
I know it's a little awkward for me, but...
Mizukami-san, please come in.
May I ask you to excuse yourself?
I'm sorry.
How did you come up with the idea?
I believe it was during the last engine battle of Part 2.
Yes, sir.
It was at the end of the second part, during the "Enjoy Life" scene.
I was dancing and the front opened a little bit.
I looked over and saw him holding out his hand.
I made eye contact with him.
I thought, "What should I do?
I couldn't just ignore it.
You mean as a performance?
Oh, yeah.
You sure? I'm sorry to say that.
As a performance.
I'm a performance person.
Well, Kanya made the hearts,
So I decided to make a heart with Kan-ya, and then I decided to make a heart with you,
So I made a heart with this and sent love power to all of you, is that correct?
Yes, thank you.
Yes, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
That's what I meant.
Yes, that's what I meant.
Thank you very much.
That was Mr. Third Base. Thank you very much.
That's funny.
At the benefit, there were many people who came wearing Mr. Sangen's mask,
That's why I've taken a few two-shots with him.
I'm sure.
There are people who even let me wear their body shape,
Thank you very much for your help, Mr. Sambasan. Always.
Thank you very much.
That's nice. But including this kind of staff,
I've never felt like this in my life on the stage.
It's been a while.
In the past, when I was performing at the third base, I used to go to the back of the stage, out of sight,
Offstage, out of sight of the stage,
The make-up artist would dance to the anthems with the audience,
Or they would hold a penlight.
But recently, it has been difficult to do so at the right time,
But recently, it's not so easy to do so at the right time,
It was nostalgic, but also very third base-like.It's nostalgic, but at the same time it's like third base.
It is true that there was such a culture.
At the time of the orca one-man show,
There was a time when all the PA staff danced with penlights. That was a long time ago.
The members of the group were also at their physical limits.
Yes, they were still in middle and high school.
At the end of the night, when it was time to go to the next show, the staff was doing the same thing, and everyone around us was doing it.
Everyone around us was getting excited, and of course the fans were getting excited, too.
It was like that. It was a lot of fun, with a sense of nostalgia and a sense of newness.
Thank you, Yasuke!
Thank you very much.
I will read more and more.
Radio name web 777
This is not a radio name, is it? It's a hair festival name. What's that?
It's a room name.
web 7777 I got it from Mr. Ooguro, beautiful.
Thank you very much.
Good evening, Mr. Oguro and Ms. Setoguchi.
I had a chance to see both parts of Yuzuki's hair festival. In conclusion, it was great.
Lumaiguro brought the middle of idols.
Basho, who brought her own view of the world to the stage and made us feel as if we had been reincarnated in a different world.
Amefura, whose fluorescent-colored costumes and cool dance moves entered the stage.
Kakko moe kasan kawachii.
Toumoku-san is so powerful that he seems to jump out into the audience.
Kakko-Lucky Funny.
Shachi was overwhelmed by the variety of paper songs.
And the research students.
Are they not cool?
Not cool at all.
Sorry.
It ends with the orca surprise mark.
Thank you very much.
The research students did a great job, didn't they?
They looked so cool.
All the groups were so energetic that I was worried if they could be invited to the next Hair Fest, but I hope Mr. O'Guro will be so kind as to invite them to the next event.
I would like to give my personal MVP to Toriko, who came to recover the MC material from last year with a new song.
Thank you for a wonderful music festival.
Promotion.
Setoguchi-san was selling his products on the street, but I was too embarrassed to approach him.
I received it.
web7777.
Thank you very much.
How about you, Mr. Oguro? What would you like to do next year if you were to hold the next Yuzuken hair festival?
But I really enjoyed the collaboration.
I would like to do it again.
Also, we didn't have a collaboration with Mr. Setoguchi this year.
If I had to give a little room for growth, I would say that there was no collaboration with Mr. Setoguchi.
In the orca part.
Yes, yes, yes. The orca part.
We played "I'm here by your side" and so on.
That was really good, wasn't it? It was like a 2021 version of Minami Shiki Flood.
That was great, wasn't it?
It was great.
I've never made anyone shake like that before.
Setoguchi-san was rapping and talking to me with his loving hands, but I just ignored him and kept on singing.
It was great.
I don't have Setoguchi-san now, so I don't know if he is still around. I can say that because Mr. Setoguchi is not here now.
If he were here, he would say he would never do it.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm going to say this, but I think we will collaborate next year. With Mr. Setoguchi.
With orcas.
What do you want to do? With orcas.
Last time it was Rocket Queen. The last time was YOU, right?
Yes, that's right.
I have done Rocket Queen with YOU, and I would like to do Toriko.
Toriko.
Yes, I might want to do Toriko.
But the choreography of that song is rather simple, so I think it would be very easy for Setoguchi-san, who has done Rocket Queen and YOU, to do it.
The choreography is specialized for dancing together.
That's why you want to do it.
Toriko. It could be the perfect song for you.
Or the perfect song for you?
Like, "Let's catch a dream together.
I see.
There is also a version that goes the other way, I guess.
Is there anything you would like to see, Popo-chan?
With Mr. Setoguchi?
Not with Mr. Setoguchi.
Not with Mr. Setoguchi?
I'd like to do this next time.
Back to the topic, I am wondering how Lou Maigro will develop from Maigro to Lou Maigro.
I don't know. It's not just one Yusuke-chan, but there is a possibility that three Yusuke-chan will join at once.
It's not impossible.
There is also a possibility that another unit will be formed.
Rumaiguro, you know, is getting better and better.
It's going to be Rumaiguroki, you know. Yusuke-chan, you know.
Indeed.
If the goro part had been taken somewhere else in Yusuki, we could have merged them together.
It's gross, isn't it? It's my element.
It's grotesque, right?
Gross.
I shot the darkest part.
That's for sure. That's why it's possible to create another group.
So we will also have to see how far Daikoku-san is willing to go.
Weekdays are pretty tough, aren't they? In this case, we all got together for four songs at Lou Maiglo.
We had lessons and sang the songs, and we checked all the vocals as well.
With Tohoku-san
It's all done in a relaxed manner.
What? That way?
No, no, no.No, no, no.
But it wasn't as cutthroat as I thought it would be.
Surprisingly?
Maybe I'm just a quick learner.
The only time I was "wigged out" was before I learned it.
Once I started learning it, I could handle it.
I could do it.
Can you still do 2 more collaborations?
In terms of how hard it is...
It was more like a feeling of happiness.
The timetable on the day was really messed up.
Daikoku's schedule is pretty messed up.
Rehearsal, rehearsal, rehearsal.
Make-up
The time for everyone to gather at the venue
Usually we take a break and prepare for the show.
Daikoku-san is the host of the event, or meets with the audience.
We have a meeting at each group's place.
Maybe we have dinner at a party.
I ate one potato from my lunch box at Torih ball.
At first
We did the show.
There was a lumigro, and then an opening, and then we'd go in between.
And then we'd have an intermission, so we'd watch everyone else perform.
And then we did our own thing.
And then we're done.
On the day of the show, there was a typhoon.
We finally decided to delay the event by 30 minutes.
I couldn't take the bullet train because of the typhoon.
We had a rehearsal in the car the day before.
But the Shinkansen stopped and I couldn't go.
I was thinking of taking the first train on the day of the rehearsal.
But it seemed like they didn't know if the first train was going to leave or not.
So I left with my family at midnight.
We left by car.
But all the highways were closed.
We arrived one minute before the rehearsal.
I mean, it was after the rehearsal.
We moved the rehearsal.
So we arrived about a minute before the rehearsal.
It was really close.
And with the help of my family.
I finally got there.
I kept in touch with the staff all night long.
I was like, "I'm sorry.
I was like, "I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Because it's Okun-san, he really has a family meeting at midnight or 1am the day before.
I mean, they're having a family meeting at midnight or 1:00 a.m. the day before.
Should I leave?
Wait for the first train.
Should I take the first train?
After all, it's too early in the morning.
In the end, it was a good decision.
Since I didn't take the first train, I'd never make it in time.
So I was going to drive to Shinjuku.
But I couldn't even make it to Shinjuku.
So I got off the train at the delivery stop and took the train to Shinjuku.
I was so excited to get off the train and go to Shinjuku.
That's right.
I was really sticking my head out.
"What are we going to do?
Popo-chan said...
Maybe you know someone here... or a friend.
Like, "Maybe your friend is here today.
I don't know.
Like, "Here's this food...
Please eat something new and relax your mind.
That's not where I was going.
I was like, "What's that?
Suddenly I got excited.
That was part of it.
With the help of many people...
I got there.
From Yuzuki's hair festival on June 3rd
From Yuzuki's hair festival on June 3 to Setoguchi's birthday
The hardest time for me was
Setoguchi's birthday party, rock-paper-scissors-scissors with all my might.
In terms of time.
Almost 24 hours.
I was up the day before.
We left in the middle of the night.
I didn't sleep well in the car.
I was up for 30 some hours.
The whole Setoguchi birthday thing was a lot of fun.
But when we asked Setoguchi-san if he had any unfinished business at the birthday party
I was wondering if there was anything you wanted to do...
I'd like to do "Zenryoku Compress and Hoi" (I'd like to do all-out compress and hoi).
It's a common talk trip among the company members.
He said he wanted to do it.
That was the hardest part of the day.
So in the middle of doing it.
I said, "It's over," and I ended it.
And things went on.
But that's part of it.
I hope it will be a good memory.
That's why, in the midst of all this
Part of it is over.
I'm pushing.
So I'm really happy to be able to do it.
So I really hope that everyoneSo I really don't know if you guys are already
Some of you got out.
Five minutes later.
After the rehearsal of Rain Hula, Ookoro-san was on standby for Rain Hula's rehearsal.
And before Tohoku's rehearsal? After the rehearsal, you were on youtube?
After the rehearsal, we filmed the first video of Amehura on youtube.
Then we went back to the rehearsal for Tohoku-san, and then we had another meeting for the second part of the show, and we prepared and made the video.
And then it was time for the show. It was a very fast and furious day.
It was a very fast day. But it was fun. I was dragged to so many places like that.
I was a little bit busy with my schedule. I like to look at behind-the-scenes vlogs of idols a lot.
For example, I like to watch vlogs of AKB's graduation performances.
I was also happy to see that, and most recently, I was happy to see the Ayaka Nation and Arin's performance, and I was also very happy to see the AKBs who were very busy.
I was also happy to see people who were very busy, so I was also happy to see that. I thought it was great that all the organizers or people who have their names on their shoulders were so great.
So, the scale may be different, but I could experience something similar, a little bit like a work experience.
It's like a work experience. You know, there are work experience programs, right? You know, you can do some kind of work experience, like at a coffee shop.
I was like, "Yes, yes, yes. If this was going on every day during the work experience, would it be better to change the environment or that?
Oh my God, the swing set.
It's a special day.
It's once a year, but, you know, the busyness of it is good. I wrote a letter to each one of them, and it's fun to spend time with them.
I guess it's because I like to do it that way.
I think that's probably because I like to do it that way, and I was having a lot of fun during the day.
We even took a photo of Setoguchi's first union, Ahsha!
Lidoa-chan was so kind as to take pictures of us.
That's also included in the making of the film.
Oh, I see.
The difference in the making of the film is that until the members came in, there's a difference in the flow of the filming.
It's rare that Lido is there, and that's the only picture that's up there.
You can see how it came to be like that in the making of the film.
Why is Okamoto-san, the stylist, in the background?
There's also a costume designer.
Why Okamoto-san, the stylist, is there in the background?
Yes, there is. Please look forward to it.
I'll call you more and more.
Wow, you've written a lot.
You know, it's great.
Room name, Takerun-san.
Well, Daikoku-san, Setoguchi-san, good evening.
This is a very long message, but I'd like to send you my impressions.
For the third time, I was able to participate in the Hair Fest, which I had longed for!
The first two parts of the festival were filled with people who are indispensable to Yuzuki's hair.
I am very grateful to Mr. Daikoku, the owner of Yuzuki, and Mr. Setoguchi, the manager of Yuzuki Hair, for their daily efforts and personalities.
I am very happy that the daily efforts and personalities of Mr. Daikoku, the owner, and Mr. Setoguchi, the manager, have continued to produce results.
We are very happy to see the cute and cuddly
Crackers, in lumaiglo, cute and cute
I'm sure I'm not mistaken!
I'm so happy to see you in your costumes and performance, and to see you in the orcas!
And which one, hmm? What?
I couldn't stop!
And all of it, oh, all of it, the performance, all of it...
Daikoku-san's performance was wonderful and, er, entertaining!
I felt that the power of Mr. Roo-Nai-san of Lulu
In the end, it seemed that only a part of the power of Mr. Nai-san of Lulu Lulu was demonstrated.
I'm glad I bought the Kakko and the water masks anyway!
And then, I was so impressed by the deliberate mockery of Mr. Tohoku.
Daikoku-san, who is collaborating with Amefura-chan's Michi
Daikoku-san and Nukiyo-chan having a scoring session on stage.
It was a precious and precious moment that could only be seen at Hair Fest.
Even though we had a lot of fun during the first and second parts of the festival
But the day wasn't over yet!
In a sense, it was the main event!
Setoguchi Birthday Festival 2022 & 2023!
I somehow managed to sneak into the venue with a same-day ticket
I had a good time chatting and solving riddles.
from the countdown to the birthday celebration
And even Daikoku-san's singing!
The volume and spirit of service was beyond my imagination
I was able to spend time in the blink of an eye.
I was finally able to take a two-shot with Mr. Setoguchi
Thanks to the full cooperation of Tokyo Mystery Circus, we were able to get a two-shot with Mr. Setoguchi.
Thank you once again!
And on stage at the Hair Fest
Today's guest appearance was decided
To all of Amefura-chan's guests who were scheduled to appear on stage today!
I'm going to say it here... to all the Amefurachans...
In the aftermath of Hair Fest
I was able to go to Lilybees yesterday
Just at the tour finale last year.
I've been to a one-man show before, but
but this was my first time at the Lilybeh event.
hairfest and also to thank you for today's
wearing Setoguchi-san's T-shirt and Daikoku-san's Aloha
I'm so glad to see you!
I'm so happy to see you!
The four of us gave a cool performance and
and the loose feeling in the MC.
The gap between the cool and cool performance and the
It was so much fun to see their individuality!
There are so many things to see and do at the Hair Fest.
I'm getting more and more captivated by all the performers.
while my DD is accelerating.
I'm tired!
Through the Hair Fest in this way
Each group interacts with each other and
of tonight's event as soon as it's hot.
become the overall guest performer, etc.
The significance of Hair's existence is becoming greater and greater.
I am very happy!
I would like to thank Daikoku-san and Yuzuki's hair
Together with
I hope that the circle of "STAPLER" will expand
I hope that the circle of STAPLER will expandWe look forward to the further expansion of the STAPLER circle.
We will continue to look forward to the further expansion of the circle of STAPLER.
Thank you very much.
That's all.
Thank you very much, Takebayashi.
Applause
That's great.
I'm so happy.
I'm curious, I'm curious, I'm curious.
I'm curious, I'm curious, I'm curious
I've been listening to you all day.
I'm sorry.
I'm curious... I'm curious...
I was searching for "drop drop".
You should listen to it, it's great.
It's really good.
Amefura's music is really good!
Yesterday, too!
In Aichi Prefecture.
They were reefing at a place called Tsunename.
We were reeving at a place called Otaka, too.
In Aichi Prefecture.
Aichi Prefecture
One part of the reef was at the same time as the other part.
But the second part was not.
There was a fan of Amefura-chan
came to the event
wearing Amefura-chan T-shirts
wearing Amefura-chan T-shirts.
That kind of thing.
Groups within StarPlaza
And the fans who come and go
I'm really happy to see that
It makes me really happy.
And Takeda Kel is no exception.
wearing Yuzuki's goods
I'm glad I went and saw the show yesterday.
I'm also very happy to hear that.
It makes me happy.
And the fans of the shirts too.
If there's anyone from the StarPlaza group...
I'd like you to go.
On the other hand, if you've never worn the shirt but you're in another group...
I'd be happy if you could come.
I'd be happy.
Fukai: That's right.
We'll alternate between the main words and the end of the show.
I'd be happy if you could come.
Oda That would be nice.
Fukai Yes.
Oda Next.
Oda Next. Mukai, I'd like to continue.
Mukai Yay!
Markon. Good evening, Setoguchi-san.
My room name is Markon.
Yuzuki's Hair Fest.
I thoroughly enjoyed the festival.
I collaborated with Amefura-chan Tohoku-san.
Daikoku-san went from being an idol to a nerd again.
He looked like he was having a great time from start to finish.
It was impressive!
I didn't expect to see Power Bo on the shirt!
Haru-chan's guess and the call
I was tired of headbanging on one side of the stage, but
It was great!
Enjoy life" at the end when everyone came out.
It has become a tradition, but it's great!
I'm sure there will be another one next year, of course.
I'm looking forward to it with excitement!
Mr. Daikoku and Mr. Setoguchi, thank you so much for your hard work.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Markon, thank you.
Applause
Powerboards.
I mean, you get to see one side of the band.
I mean, the call was great.
It's been a long time since I've seen one group.
Markon, were your shoulders crossed?
Mukai, you had your shoulders crossed.
Yeah, there was an area where they were shoulder to shoulder.
Powerboards.
All of us.
They were saying, "Hey, hey, hey!
It's all folded up.
Oh, my God.
From the stage.
Oh, man, that's a good headbang.
What's up?
Like this.
It's so funny.
But...
Powerboards were silent the whole time.
It was a headbang.
I had a little voice
It's even more powerful now.
Powerboats.
It was the first time since we opened Corona.
It was the first time I could do it with my voice.It was the first time I could do it out loud.
I'm so glad you enjoyed it.
I'm very happy.
You're so switched on.
That intro is amazing!
Power from the intro.
Asano's music
At the start of the intro...
The way he kicks it into high gear in the first 2.5 seconds is amazing.
Like that one, the intro to "Bankuru, Bankuru, Bankuru" also has a kick that really gets you going.
The kick at the beginning of the song.
Doo-doo's... that kind of thing is an important ingredient to get everyone on board at a live performance.
It's an important ingredient to get everyone on board.
Well, I'm looking forward to seeing Orca-sama.
I'm looking forward to it.
You don't seem to be stuck to your shoulders at all.
When he doesn't call out, he shows his work.
I'm not sure what it is... but there are parts where I show them as a work of art.
I think that's one of our strengths.
But this is different from that.
Well, I think everyone gets it.
Do you get it? It's a little bit disorganized.
But I really like it, and we talk about the setlist on the orca group line.
Some people said it's a bit too much, but...
But we all agreed that it's just like Orca.
What about the set list?
When we looked at the setlist, we felt it was a little too disjointed.
It was like this.
And now that showing is also a new weapon for us, are we going to do it or not?
Or, since you are the killer whale, are you going to use a setlist that is already scattered all over the place?
So we're going to go with a set list that's already scattered all over the place.
I don't think "disjointed" is the right word for you.
I don't know what to say.
So it's very live, isn't it?
My birthday isn't that neat and tidy.
Tidy?
That messy set list.
What's the point?
It's not clean and polished, it's more like...
Like a "boom".
That's what I want to tell you.
Before that, you were all sparkly.
Sparkle.
It's not a show.
It wasn't a show, it was like boxing.
I think you've got it.
Boxing.
It's not a show, it's boxing.
Let's do it!
(laughs)
No, really, but...
The setlist is really good.
You know, there are songs that are included because it's at Nagoya Castle.
You know?
There are songs that have never been included in Shachisama's show before.
It's like there are songs that have never been included in the Shachisama show.
That's what I like about it.
Compared to the past, it's really...
I don't know how to say it... it's more like a balance trend.
It's more like a statement.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
It's not balanced.
I don't want to be unbalanced.
Yeah, so...
I really want you to come.
If you've seen a killer whale, even just once...
I'm sure you'll be really excited.
And if you've never seen it before...
It's a show that will definitely draw you in.
I want all mankind to see it.
All mankind.
I really do.
I'll be waiting for you on July 22nd at Nagoya Castle.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's get back to the hairpiece.
Yes, sir.
We have a guest with the room name Silver Shirin.
Yuzuki, Mr. Setoguchi...
Yuzuki, Mr. Setoguchi, and all the staff.
Ladies and gentlemen, if there are any guests, please welcome them.
Good evening.
Thank you very much for your kindness.
Thank you very much.
I am busy sending you my impressions of Yuzuki's Hair Fest.
This was my first time to attend Yuzuki's Hair Fest, although only a part of it!
It started with a karaoke contest during the entrance of the audience.
How cool!
Mise Papa, you've got a great voice!
I know what's going on, what's going on, what's going on
It's kind of exciting, isn't it?
Mr. Setoguchi does a good job of livening things up.
Yuzuki, you're leaving from here?
And the research students are so energetic and cute!
Ah! There's Ayanano!
Rune bread came at the "Rumi Glo" show!
I knew it! She's singing!
Luna is so cute when she sings and dances.
I love the way her expression changes.
That's a good point.
Hmm?
Huh? Maimai's cute.What? Maimai is cute!
Yuzuki's cute and beautiful.
Your outfit is so cute!
The music selection is divine!
Nukaso-san, you're really making a world of your own.
I love the song!
I like the feeling of seeing something nice.
JAKKIRAI
jakkibarai
jakki-Barai
I feel like I'm getting rid of the latter with the applause of the women's exorcism.
I wonder what the next song will be?
Oh, they're all so cute!
Everyone is so cute in their own way!
Aww...
Cool!
It's Audrey's stuff.
Kakko!
Sakura Seta's pointing wink-less direct hit!
I love it!
Killer Whale for real!
Live performance is fun!
No, no, no, the dancing is too intense!
She sings, dances and smiles like this!
Studebaker's idol is a monster!
And so on and so forth.
Yuzuki and Setoguchi's personality
Yuzuki and Mr. Setoguchi's personalities made the audience feel at home.
The festival was filled with the best of each group
The festival was filled with the best of each group.
Yuzuki's role may have been her own, but
Yuzuki-chan's role may have been Yuzuki's, but the more I push her, the more she pushes me!
Setoguchi-san's sharp and sharp thrusts in some places
I enjoyed the festival very much!
I wish I could have gone to the second part too!
I wish I could have stayed for Setoguchi-san's birthday too!
Well, let me just let my heart's voice drip from the live
I'm just letting my mind drift during the show.
Anyway, it was a lot of fun!
I don't do this once every 6 months or so!
Like Yuzuki's hair festival 3.5
That's how much fun the festival was!
Take care of yourselves, everyone!
Yuzuki's Hair Fest 3.5 meeting
Good luck!
It's already been decided.
It's a done deal.
No, but...
Nice Shirin, you have good taste.
Thank you.
It's funny... we have a great view. Where will you go next? Where will we go next?
Where would you like to go next?
It's nice.
I'm not sure if it's better to have one festival or two.
But it's a tough call... it's a tough call... but if we don't divide it into two parts, it'll be more of a flurry...
I think it's better to have two parts of the festival than one part, but it's difficult to decide.
And also, guests can say, "Who do you want to see?" and "Who do you want to see?
We can also have some of the guests be named "who's who." So, yes, I'm looking forward to it.
Last time, Star Beams had a band... a band...
We're looking forward to having guests who transcend the boundaries of idols.
I'm looking forward to seeing you in a loincloth by yourself.
I'm sure you'll make friends with the staff and the people outside too... you're shagging me, aren't you?
I'm sure you've made friends with Hiiichan and returned home.
I'd like to collaborate with Yuzuki's room at the festival.
I want to collaborate with Aikoran's character... but Daikoku-san is hosting the festival, so...
I'm going to do my best to get Yuzuki's character in the festival, but since it's a festival hosted by Daikoku, then I'll have to do my best.
I'd like to talk to your sisters as well, as I've been doing in the chat room right now.
If I do that, I might be able to get into one of the three major festivals.
I'm talking about the big three festivals.
Join Alive, Tamasonee, Yutsuki no Yubetsu no Yaome festival, Fuji Rock...
Fuji Rock... so I'm going to be in there...
There are so many, so many famous festivals
One of the most famous festivals, yes, but it's a rock festival, isn't it?
Teefoo at Jam, Moon Room Festival, Spark...
We'll take care of all the details.
That's great! Dream big!
It's great that we're going to perform at the Yutsuki no Yuuki no Okubo festival!
But that's how we want the festival to be.
Have you ever been asked if you want to participate? You haven't received any offers to perform at the Yuzuki Room festival yet?
Not yet. It's still recognized as a STAPRO event.
I see. That's right. So next time...
Next time, we'll be a little more open.
But, you know, when you think about it... how many times have you been to Sparkfest, which I'll be performing at this year?
Second time. Second time.
It's the second time, and it's the first time since the first time, but it's so big!
I'd like to hear the essence of what you're talking about.
How can you make it that big?
I'll ask him this summer.
Let's ask the organizer.
I'm going to remind the organizer of that.
I'd like to absorb some of their techniques.
Let's make it a big festival!
But really, since we've come all the way to ZEPP, let's see what's next.
What's next?
A hall?
That's nice.
I wonder if there will be a festival at a hall.
I'm sure there will be a festival at the hall.
If it goes that far, Yuzuki will cry for sure!
I'm sure Yuzuki would cry.
Isn't it too early?Isn't it too early?
I don't know, but if we go to an arena or something, I might feel like I'm going to cry.
Even in a hall?
I've been to a lot of halls.
I thought it was fast.
That's true.
We'll have to save it.
No, but... we'll expand next year, too.
But, you know... if it's a hall or something...
Will there be more performers?
No, but time-wise...
Then maybe two days.
Day 1 and Day 2?
You're just saying that?
Maybe Day 1 and Day 2.
Then we can call more people per day.
We can do 5,5 or something like that.
We can do 5,5.
You can do it.
Dream big.
Let's make some things come true.
Sounds interesting.
I'd like to spread the word.
Let's spread it!
You're really something, Mr. Osawa.
Your knowledge about idols in general is increasing.
I've been able to do the pressing since this year.
That's a big deal.
When I couldn't do it.
When I was pushing hard and single-mindedly
That was fun, but...
Pushing is fun, isn't it?
It's fun to do oshimashi
Because there is no end to the sites
Because you never get to go there
You never get to go there.
You know...
When I was only pushing Masaki-chan...
When Morning Musume performs.
Because of how rare it was.
I was lucky if I got to go a few times a year.
So it was a little bit like...
It was like winning the lottery.
It was fun.
But the moment I made my first appearance...
At this point, you can't say how many times you've been.
Over the course of a year.
You know, the times you score points with your favorite group.
Festivals are fun, too.
When it comes to that...
You went to see Ocha-no-Ma's concert the other day, right?
I've been interested in him ever since.
I've been watching his videos.
I feel like I'm going to get more and more admirers.
I'm sure I'll be able to get more and more admirers.
Even in StarPlaza...
I'm getting more and more guesses.
I don't know, before...
I used to think of them as my cute little sister group.
But when you start to have your own idols...
You become a nerd.
Right?
That's why, in the ultimate sense...
If you start to guess yourself, you're the best.
You mean you're a fan of Yuzuki Oubre?
That's right.
I wonder how you feel about that.
So, you know...
I'm going to start promoting myself.
If you start promoting yourself...
If you start promoting yourself with that bird's eye view...
But that's strong, isn't it?
Then you know yourself, you know yourself.
If you do that...
You can become your ideal guesser, right?
Muzu
It's the strongest.
You can create your own ideal.
So you can impose your ideal on yourself
You can impose it on yourself, right?
Then the gap between ideal and reality
The gap between the ideal and the reality will disappear.
Because you can make your own ideal
Because you put your wish into yourself
Unwilling
What do you think of this proposal?
I'm being nodded at.
But if you could do that...
I'm sure you'd be a very strong idol.
It's strong, isn't it?
I just don't know if I have the emotional strength to push it.
I hadn't really thought about it yet.
I'm glad.
I'll put that in there.
I'll give it to her.
Izumi-san's looking at me like I'm crazy.
Mr. Izumi...
I don't know what he's talking about.
I'm a bit...
When I first started talking, I didn't know what to expect.When I first started talking, I had to give it up.
It was a good landing spot.
I think we have that in common.
We talk off the cuff.
I'm talking with a lot of passion.
And then one day...
There's no one there for me.
It's a common thing, isn't it?
It's sad, isn't it?
Let's continue.
Room name Bake-chan.
Good evening, Yuzuki and Setoguchi.
This week's Bake-chan.
Thank you for your hard work at Yuzuki's Hair Festival on June 3rd.
This was the third year in a row that I've attended this event.
I've been to this festival three years in a row, and I can see a lot of my guesses in this festival.
There are a lot of guesses at this festival.
Ayano joined the Stapler research students.
Yuzuki's special hair-only unit, Lumaiglo
Team Shirt-chan's
Team Shirt-chan's cute little sister Batten Shoujo-tai, with Moeka, who is Setoguchi-san's guess because of her cool dance moves Ame-Flashy, with Setoguchi-san's to
Team Shirt with Yuzu Daikoku-san, the organizer of the Hair Festival, who is also the organizer of Yuzuki's Hair Festival.
Setoguchi's first union, as mysterious as solving a scrap puzzle
After three years of attending Yuzuki no Hair Fest, I'm convinced that I'm not the only one who has been to Yuzuki no Hair Fest.
I'm already looking forward to next year's Hair Fest, so please start negotiating with the performers now!
ps I also enjoyed Setoguchi-san's birthday party.
The booth isn't amazing, it's just amazing.
It's great to have Setoguchi-san's to I saw Seisachi's insta-chan's insta-chan
She said she's going to edit the shot with Setoguchi, so please wait a bit... and then she went on there like a happy channel...
Boo hoo!
And the second one is with Mr. Setoguchi, a.k.a. Mr. Setoguchi, and I was like, "Wait a minute, what's this?
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get a copy of it.
I see. I like Karen and Miyu.
She's really into him... probably due to this week's episode with Karen... but I can't stop thinking about that gorilla hole...
Boo-hoo, Arne!
Lucky, when we were in Taiwan, we went to an event called "Staplerocalism" in Taiwan.
That was the first time I saw something that surprised me...
He was shaking tapioca milk tea to the tune of "Cheers Japan, Cheers Japan." He was shaking it so much on stage.
He was doing it so much on stage... he was talking through the microphone in Kaya's ear... and he was doing it so loudly.
He said he was so surprised on stage in Taiwan that he laughed so hard, right?
I was watching the stream, and I saw that Io, the manager, was having a meeting with Lucky, and the contents of the meeting were about the guest, the guest who was suddenly on Staccom.
The guest is a collaborator of Stacomu, and they've been working together on how to welcome Daikoku-san or someone like that when he comes in suddenly.
We've been discussing how we'd welcome Daikoku-san, for example, if he suddenly came on the show.
We had a balloon or something that made some kind of noise, and we came in and said, "We've started a collaborative distribution.
I said, "I'm starting a collaborative distribution," and he said, "Welcome!
And she made it happen.
She's shy and very serious... but I was with her at the Stacomu Awards... and I've been so nervous all day.
That's one of the things that's so attractive about you, Mi-chan.
I'd like him to come, because he's never actually been here before.
I'm from Tohoku, so it's hard to make time for you, but even if you have time, I'm always looking forward to seeing you.
I'm still going to do my best even if I do, even if you write a lot, I'm talking too much
I'm going to shut up now because we were talking in between.
Good evening. It's already been more than a week since Yuzuki's Hair Fest.
It's been more than a week since Yuzuki's Hair Fest was held, and I hope you're all doing well.
Because of this connection and bond, everyone's roommates watched the live performance with peace of mind and trust, and the performers were also able to perform with 200 percent more power than before.
I enjoyed both parts of the show because of this connection. My personal highlight was the collaboration between Yuzukichan's Iginari and his wife.
It was great to see Yuzuki-chan smiling like he did when he scored the Masanaa.
Thank you to everyone involved for wishing us another 4th wonderful festival.
I'm really happy to hear you say that after 200 times of this festival, I'm very happy to hear you say that.
Thank you very much.
This was my first time to attend Yuzuki's Hair Festival and I had so much fun I was sweating.
I'm a fan of AmeFlash, especially Hana-chan, and I'm so happy to hear that Yuzuki-chan is also a fan of Hana and Hana-chan.
The collaboration with Yuzuki-chan was really cute and I especially enjoyed the name calling part.
I thought it was genius when Yuzuki-chan and Yuzuki-chan of the Rain Hula came out together at the end.
Thank you very much for the information from Mr. Pudding.
When we went to the rehearsal together a few days ago, it was a little bit like we were doing something here and there.
We always do skits, improvisation, calls, etc. So we said we'll let you know when we decide on those things, and we left for the day.
On that day, Yuzuki-chan asked me to call her Yuzuki-chan and ask her to call me Yuzuki when the time comes.
I don't know at what timing, but she asked me to call her Yuzuki when she was with me, and I wondered when that would be.
I was wondering when the turn started and I said "Yuzuki" at the end of the turn when everyone was saying "hey hey", so I thought "I'm a genius too" with Puddin
That's why I'm going to do it later.Fabo also had his first experience of singing out loud and he was so excited! The other students of the Staffura group were also very passionate and the time passed by very quickly!
We are looking forward to next year's event again! Thank you very much for your room name, purple!
What song was that?
That was Bunkuru!
Bunkuru is the song "Let Me Be God" and there's a pocket for the earphones, but the pocket broke and the earphones came off.
I thought maybe the pocket had come off where I hooked it, but I couldn't do it because the earphones were hanging around the whole time, so I rushed to fix it.
It was the B-melody, I threw up on the A-melody, and I probably threw up on the bunkle.
I was dancing at full power, and my costume broke.
So I went to the B-melody and I thought, what should I do, but I have a microphone, so I thought I'd sing, and I did, and the three of them looked at me and said, "Hmmm...
And then the three of them looked at me like, "Hmmm," and said, "Yeah," and then they sang.
I was probably thinking the same thing as Murasaki-san at the same time.
But the way everyone adapted to the orca's little troubles...
I feel that sense of teamwork is something I've been seeing a lot lately.
I think that because live performance is a living organism, problems are bound to occur, but only the members of the group can solve those problems.
I think it's great that we can do that even without exchanging words, and I really appreciate it.
It's not easy to have a hole in your life, but you sang to me without getting upset at all.
But you sang it without getting upset at all.
And yes, thanks to the three of you, I was able to go in as if nothing had happened.
I thought that the fact that all three of them were thinking about the same thing when they made the decision was one of the strengths of Shachi, so I could work with confidence.
I can work with peace of mind.
I really feel safe.
But this was really a big event for me.
I was touched by everyone's kindness, but in the meantime, the staff worked really hard to fix it.
You're right... we're a great team!
Thank you.
This is Yuzuki, my room name is Robin Kopp, and I'd like to welcome you to Yuzuki's Hair Fest.
I participated in all 20232 minutes, and I'd like to send you my impressions. This was the third dance, and the first voice out, and it was the best one yet!
I am glad that everyone liked the show because of the personality of Yuzuki-chan and Mr. Setoguchi, and the atmosphere of the show was filled with a sense of family.
The hellish time before the show started was filled with the audience's laughter and laughter of Setoguchi-san, Ogawa-san, and others.
The duet with Yuzuki-chan was very moving, but I was personally impressed by Nise Papa's singing ability and the song selection.
In the second part, I was so moved to hear Lumpin' Chatmonchy sing solo. Afterwards, I was lucky enough to be able to stand in line with the audience and talk with them for the first time in a while.
As a participant in the STAPLER research student t-shirt, I was thrilled to see that the experience I had gained on stage was being put to good use, and the audience was well involved in the spectacle.
I was also impressed by the way they were able to involve the audience in the performance. The Rumi Glo trio is a veteran trio, but they have more than just experience.
I would love to see them again in the future, so I'm waiting for them to hold another event with their original songs.
Batten girl body is graceful, graceful, graceful, Mizuki's favorite son-taku set 3 weeks ago way.
Yuzuki-chan's benefit time was also very funny!
Rain Flash is a reliable stage performance that increases the club atmosphere of Zep.
The collaboration of Yuzuki and the road was so exciting.
Aira-chan's happenings were also very unique and good. Iginari Talk's benefit version of the deliberate handle expert was a big winner!
I felt that the song "I can't lose" shone differently when I heard it in the stapler, and Lucky-san's performance in the corner after the song was also great.
Team Killer Whale, the smallest group at the festival I attended a little while ago, is definitely one of the most athletic groups with a long history of activity, but I was still blown away by their performance.
I was reminded of this by the overwhelmingly enjoyable, all-out, all-out backstage action, and your captivation overwhelmingly captured my heart.
After witnessing the backs of such reliable seniors, the enjoyment of life in the all-lineup was euphoric! The sight of all the people mingling together was blissful and a time I never wanted to see end!
That's all from Mr. Robin Cop, thank you very much!
I'm so happy!
I'm so glad you wrote it down so well, because your captivation really captured my heart, especially that part.
I was a little nervous because it was my first time performing, but I'm so glad you enjoyed it.
And before the show started, the fake dad was... personally, mvp... amazing to me.
It was an empty venue.
I was really excited when he started to sing, and then he sang a song from a cartoon called "Beck," which is a cartoon called "Great Full Sound," and it was at the very end of the third stage, and I thought, "This is going to be boring for the audience.
He started to sing, and the audience was bored, but when he started singing, they responded to his voice, and the audience came in.
When Papa was singing "Moonlight", people kept coming in.
My dad bought a lot of stuff, but I think he was really influenced by something called "Sapopochanbekku.
I was influenced by it, and when I told you, you looked so tense
Please tell him that it's going to be restricted admission when he sees more and more people coming in after this
Buber
I thought at the time that it was impressive that people would gather like that at festivals, but when I heard what you just said, I wondered if you were talking about this.
I really wish you hadn't said that.
I'm really sorry... but there are a lot of comments about fake dads... when I read things like this.
So, you know, people who come to Kanna often hear Nise Papa's singing voice.
There's a big good-bye show coming up later on, so please look forward to it.
I'm sure you'll enjoy it... but I've only recently started wearing cat colors.
Most of you have never heard Nise Papa's singing voice.
He's so good! He sings "I'm so good!" with energy and enthusiasm!
She's so good! She's so good, right?
I heard that Yuthey's room is a little bit like a hunchback's room, and the staff is so hunched over that even Ms. Mizukami ends up as a collectible.
I hope you'll continue to enjoy the show as much as we do, as long as we have time.
I'd like to introduce Mr. Roychi, whose room name is Daikoku-san, Mr. Setoguchi-san, good evening, good evening, first time.I'm really happy to be able to go to see all the different groups.
Of course the girls who performed in this show are all really attractive, so you really have to see them to understand what they have to offer.
So I'm really happy that you can experience that in Yuzuki's room.
I hope this event will be a win-win situation for everyone.
I wonder if Setoguchi-san's birthday party will be held next year... I wonder why it was postponed...
I'd rather not have a birthday than to have one in this place because of the Corona disaster...
I see... but it turned out to be a great event.
I'm glad we were able to collect the two years' worth of donations. I hope we can do it again next year.
It was fun... the clock suddenly appeared... at 11:45... and it's my birthday in 15 minutes.
I've been asked twice what I want to do before my birthday... and it's really something like Mr. Scrap!
It was kind of fun... like a real-life escape game... and it's been a while since I've solved a riddle.
I wonder if they made a special riddle for us to solve.
It's a riddle that's related to the car, and it's a lot of fun.
It was a lot of fun, and we were having a lot of fun doing that event.
I'm not going to boo-boo, so maybe he was strong, but he was also strong, so he was invincible, right?
He was in his invincible mode, like he was saying, "I'm not going to do it anyway, so I'm going to say it until morning.
I've been in a high state of tension for most of the night... yes... I sang two songs late at night... yes...
I sang two songs late at night.
I hope we can do it in February, so we can celebrate your birthday next time.
Okay, front, back, front and back.
Front and back ok boo boo.
Good evening Yuzukichan Setoguchi-san, I attended both parts of Yuzuki's hair festival.
I'd like to start by saying that the Tokaido Shinkansen was cancelled in the morning due to a typhoon, but I was able to attend both parts of Yuzuki's Hair Festival.
I really wanted to see the live performance of Yuzuki's unit "Lumaiglo" and "Team Shirt", so I took a train from my hometown Mie to Nagoya, then a limited express train from Nagoya to Kanazawa, then a Hokuriku Shinkansen from Kanazawa to Tokyo, and then a train from Kanazawa to Shinjuku.
It took more than 7 hours one way and I had to stand almost all the way in a nonreserved seat because the reserved seats were full.
I almost lost heart thinking that I might not make it to the venue in time, but I managed to arrive at the venue at 2:40 p.m.
I was so relieved to see Yuzuki, my favorite Yuzuki's unit "Lumaiglo", perform "Hatsukoi Cider" that I almost cried with tears in my eyes.
I was about to cry, but I held it in, and at that moment, I was so glad that I didn't give up and went to the venue.
All the songs were covers, but I knew them all, so I was able to call out to them, and it was a great live show where I could enjoy myself and feel the passion and unity of the audience.
Yuzuki-chan left the stage and went to the back of the stage once during the live in the car.
I could feel the bond between the three of them as they sang Yuzuki-chan's part together in the car.
Yuzuki-chan's performance after she came back to the stage was especially worth seeing.
I enjoyed the festival as a roommate of Yuzuki-chan's and enjoyed seeing her various expressions during the live.
Master, master, master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master, yes master.
In my mind, Team Kururanaka is the most addictive and powerful group, an idol group that once you fall in love with them, you can't stay away!
This moment is the most enjoyable than any other venue on earth. Thank you for holding the best festival with such passion and togetherness.
Thank you very much for reading this long article. Please hold Yuzuki's Hair Festival again next year!
Thank you to Yuzuki, Setoguchi-san, the performers, staff, and roommates for all your hard work!
June 3rd was an unforgettable day! Thank you so much!
It's great that you came straight from the first time you saw us!
I could have come a little earlier, but I had to go through Kanazawa once and was on my feet for over 7 hours.
We had to stop at Nagoya, so we had to go from Nagoya to Shizuoka, and it was pretty much a disaster.
But we still wanted to see the show, so we were on our feet for more than 7 hours, which must have been really hard.
Thank you so much for coming.
I'm sure there were people who wanted to go but couldn't, depending on the area, but it was because of the support of my roommates that we were able to make this festival possible.
I really wanted everyone to be able to see the festival, so I feel a sense of regret, so when I can do it again, I will do even better than usual and even better than before.
I'm going to prepare a lot of things so that I can repay you all, so please look forward to it.
I really hope that you can look forward to it until then.
I feel sad and disappointed, but I'm glad that people wanted to go and see the show.
I am happy that you wanted to go and see the show, so please look forward to the 4th show so that we can live up to your expectations.
Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to the fourth edition, and thank you all so much.
Hey, then, Roof Name Egg and I, Yuzuki-chan, Setoguchi-san, and all the staff, thank you for all your hard work on Yuzuki's Hair Fest!
I had so much fun and used up so much energy I had cramps in my legs after I got home!
Yuzuki-chan was divine! Not only as the organizer of the event, but also as the unit collaborator and the team shirt performer, her performance on stage was outstanding!
Her dancing and singing were powerful and heavy, her expression was confident, and she was a shining star of Stardust on the stage.
I don't know whether Yuzuki is an angel or a goddess.
I can't tell if Yuzuki-chan is an angel or a goddess. I was so moved to see how much Yuzuki-chan has grown through Yuzuki's hair, and thank you Setoguchi-san and the scrappers for a wonderful time until late!
Thank you all for taking care of me outside of the event.Word of mouth is the strongest.
Yes, and everyone's writing skills are so strong.
It's very concise and easy to understand.
That's why I've been so supported.
That's why I'm going to see Ms. Shiko Takane this weekend, too.
Takane no nama no shiko-san and I are going to have a talk trip.
And the week after next, we have the release event, so we'll have a lot of opportunities to see each other, so I'd like to see you as much as possible.
I hope you can come and see us as much as possible.
I know it's not easy since we're using all your vacations, but I'd like to ask you to run until July, even though it's a vacation for all of us.
I know it's a holiday for all of you, but I'd like you to take the first half of August off so that we can get the shirts ready for you.
We can only take the first half of August off, but we'll be back for the second half.
I'd like to create many opportunities to meet with you, but I'm not sure if you'll be able to see me again in the second half.
She's a really cute idol, so I'd like to collaborate with her.
I think that if we collaborate with her, we might be able to see a cute orca that we don't usually see.
On the other hand, I'd also like to see Takaneko in super super boxing mode.
Do you want to do that?
I keep saying boxing.
Killer whales are not live, they are boxing.
It's a sport. That's why it's boxing.
Tahmin and Orca are fighting each other.
It's a clash.
So I'm gonna open up my Corona and it's not gonna be like that.
Boxing.
Pressure on pressure on pressure.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's good.
Dialogue with Mr. Takaneko
And TTT is our usual
communication university, we can enjoy it more.
There are quite a lot of games this time, too.
Talk theme
The theme of the talk is something we've been working on for a long time, and we'll have some of your captivating secrets.
There will also be a secret story about your captivation.
There will also be a secret story about the new song.
I see.
What's the story?
I can't tell you.
There are secret stories about the choreography and so on. Actually, there are stories about how they felt,
I think those who come to the talk trip will be able to hear such things,
I am sure you will make many discoveries.
Talk trip tickets are relatively inexpensive, around 2,000 yen,
I think it's a good idea to have a talk trip.
I talk too much for 90 minutes.
Also, June is the month of June Bride.
So the costumes will be based on that motif, and we sent them out yesterday.
You mean white?
Yes, white. Not a dress or anything, but something white.
It's not like a dress, but a little white.
This time, we will have a variety of special events.
There will be a photo session and a video session.
We don't do a lot of video shoots, so we'll do them frequently.
This is the only place where you can see the costumes,
I hope you will come and see them.
We are looking forward to seeing you.
Yes, please do.
The venue is relatively close to Nagoya, so you can get there by train.
Shinkawa.
Yes, at Shinkawa.
I'll be waiting for you.
Yes, please.
I will make the announcement as it is.
First of all, on June 28th,
our second EP called "Awaiting Bear" will be released.
This time, we have teamed up with Kenta Matsuguma for this EP, which contains 4 wonderful songs.
There will be a CD and an M-card, and the design of the M-card will be random.
The CD one comes with a booklet and so on.
Both are annoying. Both are annoying, right?
So I hope you will get both of them.
I think it is very rare to see everyone wearing a bear, so I hope you will experience it too. Experience?
I hope you will take in the experience and enjoy it in your body.
I hope you will enjoy it.
The CD also includes an instrumental.
You can sing it in the car. You can sing along in the car.
I'm quite happy with the instrumental tracks, because I like to hear the background sound.
You have a strong sound in each song.
So I would like you to listen to the details of his performance, so please enjoy both the instrumental and the sung parts.
We are also currently holding a release with this "waiting wear".
The next time is the week after next in the Kanto area.
Please come and visit us in Makuhari Shin Toshin and Kameido.
On July 9, we will be holding a diner shirt event, part of which will be a birthday party for the Ogle season.
The second part will be a performance produced by the members.
The second part will be a performance produced by the members. This will also be held at a place called Diamond Hall in Shinzaka, very close to Nagoya Station.
There will also be songs that we haven't sung in a very long time, so there will be a lot of different kinds of performances,
I know there will be people who are not Yuzu fans, but everyone is welcome to join us.
We are confident that our live performance will be truly entertaining, so please come and enjoy it.
What about costumes?
Costume?
We are short of cloth.
We are running out of cloth for costumes.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, but you've allocated the cost to another area, so please use it at all this time.
Thank you very much. Please use it for Mr. Orca.
Thank you very much.
The second part is a performance produced by the members.
We can shout, we can dance, we can even put the word "shout" in the title,
This is a performance of the killer whale....
And it's like a set, and recently we've all been able to do it with our bodies and our voices,
So we are going to have a hard live performance.
So, if it says "you can shout and dance," I am thinking that there will be a lot of gutsy songs like that.
Yes, that's true. So, after the birth of Daikoku-san's solo, I was filled with love, congratulations, and a cute feeling,After all, that's how it should be. So, after the birth of Mr. Daikoku's solo, I was filled with love, congratulations, and a cute feeling,
I think that Yuzuki's birthday will also be quite a blowout,
I am sure that Yuzuki's birthday performance will also be quite a blowout.
I guess you are a bit of a scatterbrain, aren't you?
I think the 722 will be held at Nagoya Castle in a big way. So the 9th of July is a little bit in the foreground, don't you think?
It is often thought to be in the foreground, but it is a good time to go to this park.
But by going to this park
I think this live concert will be a great opportunity to raise the spirits of the people in the photos.
So please come to Nagoya on April 9 and the week of April 9 as well.
I'm sure you'll be very excited to hear the sound of the park two weeks before the show.
I'm sure you'll be excited to hear the sound of the park two weeks in advance, so let's accelerate our efforts at that time.
I know you're going to the gym right now, and I've been working out a lot, so I've been working really hard this summer to get abs, so please come and see the grooves in my abs.
I think the groove on the 9th and the water on the 22nd will be different.
I think the groove is getting deeper because I've gone from doing it only at the gym to doing it at home too.
I'm going to bring out the best in you, so please look forward to it.
For more information, please visit our website, Instagram, Twitter, etc. That's all for now, thank you very much.
Let's learn from Mr. Mizukami!
Okay, let's get right to it. Today I'd like to introduce you to...
Today's topic is "Escape from the Puzzle Castle," a real-life escape game.
what kind of lecture is it?
Escape from the Puzzle Castle is a story about a heroic and mysterious hero who tries to defeat the Demon King in order to save a town that has become full of mysteries.
The story is about a heroic and mysterious hero who must save the city from a mysterious evil king.
This game can be played by one player while switching between characters, but it is also possible to use the call tool with everyone in a remote location,
You can also play with other players at a distance by using a call tool,
You can also share the information you have obtained and the solution methods you have come up with with each character while using a call tool,
The game is designed to be played in a lively atmosphere.
I like the game screen.
It is made in 2D.
Thank you very much.
The game has been available for play since last June 9.
It looks like a free trial version for one player is actually available on the special site.
Please take a look.
It's somewhat nostalgic, isn't it? The sound is also like 8-bit.
Please enjoy it while listening to the sound.
That's all from Scrap!
The trial version is great!
Please check out the special site
Please check out the special site "Puzzle Caster" and try it!
You can do it in a browser?
Yes, it's very easy to join.
It's like Rocket Queen.
Yes, just like .a.
Thank you very much.
That's all.
That's all. Thank you very much.
So this time it was over 2 hours, and over 3 hours if you put the two of us in loincloths together.
I appeared to you a lot. Today, too.
Really, I mean, a thumbnail. I'd like to introduce a few more thumbnails first.
This one is from Mr. Hiroko of the room name Keroro. This way!
The 150th, oh, that's it, when we had the benefit party.
This one, clap. We all posed in this way at the award ceremony afterwards.
Thank you very much. It's really nice. It's fun to see all the different variations of the award show.
You took screencaps of everything. It's so much fun. There are two mysterious people and two mysterious men.
Yes, this is what I got. Thank you very much.
Here is another one from Mr. Hiroro of Keroro. This way!
The 52nd, Kanamin's remote.
Yes! I got a tanpremora from Kanamin. At that time.
She was so cute. This is it.
Kanamin came and after that, Kanamin made a surprise announcement that Reni-chan would be the next guest.
That's the 52nd time. I was still in the beginning of my 52nd show. Really.
But it's been Corona since then. So, it was probably right after Yuzuki's room started.
I mean, I feel like I've been in Corona ever since I started working here.
Thank you very much. Angel, you are so cute. Thank you very much.
Next, we have a room name from Asu. Here it is!
Ah, last time.
This one!
Isn't it really good?
Oh, man.
Illustration.
Oh, man. Hana-chan is doing the "choky" thing,
It's funny, isn't it?
She's holding a penlight that says "Moeka," and Moeka-chan is saying, "Who is the person of shame?
It's really funny. She's a good illustrator.
Yes, it is. It's a night and day.
It's amazing. Very detailed. Thank you very much. Nice illustration.
Amazing. Thank you so much for sending us thumbnails that are truly full of personality.
The thumbnails are changing more and more, so please take a look at them.
So, we have been running the Yuzukin Hair Festival for two weeks now, and it has been a really good two weeks.
As we have received quite a few messages, there is certainly a lot of desire to do it again this year.
Mountains. It's certainly mountains.
It's definitely mountains.
I don't think it has to be in the summer.
I don't know when it will be, but I definitely want to hold the fourth Yuzuki Hair Festival,
I would like to work hard on Yuzuki's hair every week so that I can show you an even better Hair Fest than this year's one.
Thank you all for your constant support.
Let's enjoy Yuzuki's hair from next week as well.
Today, Mr. Setoguchi was absent, but the first half of the show was Mr. BOT, and the second half was Mr. Popoguchi.
And we had Mr. Popoguchi for the second half. Next week, I am sure Mr. Setoguchi will be here, so please look forward to seeing Yuzuki's hair as usual again.
Then I would like to end. I'm sad, I'm sorry to leave.
Do you want to AT?
I think I've already done a lot of AT.
Setoguchi-san was shaking his head a lot.
Look at that Mr. T, he's got a cold look in his eyes. His eyes are not smiling.
It was after 23:00. There are people watching the show, you know.
Next week's show will be more substantial, and I'm sure we'll have a lot of content.
I would like to make it more intense, not in terms of time, so please look forward to it.
Thank you very much for your time today.negative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
mmm
Hm
[ED]
Thank you for watching to the end.
undefined